( Watch on Kissasia.vip & KonFlix.vip )
=No Doubt In Us=
(Adapted from the Manman comic No Doubt in Us)
=Episode 12=
Your disguise isn't clever.
Here's some money.
You should go.
I know the nearby terrain well.
I can take you
wherever you want to go.
Take her away.
Watch her closely.
Yes.
Your Majesty.
The marching route is confidential.
Your Majesty, how do you think
the Dada people found out?
There's a traitor.
Please send a letter to Xiao...
Prince Xiaoyao.
Tell him what has happened
these past two days.
Yes.
And...
Please do not tell
Xu Yu about the ambush.
I don't want her to worry.
Yes.
The prince comes to Fengyi Palace
every day to review memorials.
It must be that His Majesty ordered
the Empress to guide him.
Aunt, you must have misunderstood.
What memorials require Xu Yu's guidance?
Is the Xu family trying to seize power?
Or are they trying to corrupt Jinming?
Aunt, please do not listen to
the slander of petty people.
Look, isn't the prince
reviewing memorials?
This should be like this.
Such a deep bond as in-laws.
They are only admiring flowers and art.
Just some elegant pastimes.
Summon Xu Yu to Ci'an Palace.
Yes.
(Ci'an Palace)
Mother.
Kneel down.
Have I done something wrong?
Kneel down now!
I thought your family
had upright values.
I never expected you
to commit such disgraceful acts.
Disgraceful acts?
Jinyun is fighting on the battlefield.
Instead of sharing his burdens,
you have an affair with Jinming.
What?
Mother, I can explain.
Someone!
(She is)
(going to kill me?)
Xu Yu.
Mother.
Do you remember what His Majesty
said to you before his departure?
I also hope that
Xu Yu won't get hurt
under any circumstances.
Whatever happens,
await my return for final judgment.
You are the Empress.
I will not kill you for now.
But from today onward,
you're not to step out of Fengyi Palace.
Mother.
Before His Majesty's departure,
he instructed me
to supervise the prince
in court affairs.
Today, the prince didn't want
to attend the matchmaking at the garden,
so he asked me to come and persuade you.
But unexpectedly, you didn't appear.
Someone!
Summon Jinming to Ci'an Palace.
Yes.
Empress Dowager.
The Third Prince has arrived.
It's a trap.
Who is spreading rumors about me,
saying I go to Fengyi Palace daily?
It must be that upstart.
Who is it?
Consort Zhao.
He wears gold and silver daily.
He's annoyed that Consort Zhao
looks more extravagant than him.
But Your Highness, I must remind you.
Now, Prince Ning
has gone to Ci'an Palace too.
My uncle has gone too?
Won't that make things worse?
Not only that.
He'll surely make false accusations,
saying you two have an affair.
What are you doing?
Going to Ci'an Palace
to poison them all.
Are you insane?
Where are you going?
Going to Ci'an Palace
to see if you can think of an idea
to rescue the Empress.
Think of an idea?
What if I can't?
Then poison them all.
Terrible idea.
All terrible ideas.
- Going or not?
I'm not going to be a coward.
Empress Dowager.
Today, I heard a palace rumor
about the Empress,
so I came to verify it.
Now, it seems the Empress
has indeed acted improperly.
The palace has its own rules.
It's not your place to interfere.
I am His Majesty's uncle after all.
It's my duty to purify the palace.
Otherwise, if this rumor spreads out...
Enough!
Mother!
Mother.
There's a way.
The Grand Preceptor invites the consorts
to the imperial garden to pray
for repelling exorcism.
The Empress will suffer no more.
Here.
It's time.
Physician Jiang.
Please.
What's this?
Lately, the Empress
has been speaking improperly
because she's lovesick for His Majesty.
Evil spirits have entered her.
I have a way to cure it.
(What are they doing now?)
Uncle.
My sister-in-law even burned
Mother's favorite painting.
If this gets out,
the royal dignity will be lost.
Besides, you won't be able
to hold your head up.
Isn't that right?
Your Highness.
You're close kin and highly respected.
I have an impertinent request.
May I use your blood
as a medicinal catalyst?
You won't refuse, will you?
Of course my uncle won't refuse.
He cares most for us juniors.
Isn't that so?
Please follow me.
Your Highness, please.
Close the door.
Even if you sent your uncle away,
must you make your scandal
in Fengyi Palace
known to all?
Mother.
Let the prince tell you
why he came to Fengyi Palace.
Mother.
Didn't you tell me to go
to Fengyi Palace to discuss my marriage?
But I don't want to marry.
So I asked her to persuade you.
If she succeeded,
I'd review memorials
in the study every day.
When did I tell you
to discuss marriage with her?
Didn't she make you
review memorials in Fengyi Palace?
Where is Zhao Qiluo?
I know.
She's praying in the garden.
Summon her inside.
Aunt.
Zhao Qiluo.
Didn't Lady Tao teach you
a harsh lesson?
Aunt, please calm down.
I did send someone
to deliver a message to the prince.
But I did it all for His Majesty.
That day, I clearly saw
them acting intimately.
That's why I resorted to this plan.
It was only due to
my concern for His Majesty.
I beg for your mercy.
You slandered me and the regent prince.
This is a grave offense.
You also forged a decree.
That makes the crime even worse.
Xu Yu.
Aunt.
From today, you're stripped
of your Noble Consort title.
Demoted to Virtuous Consort.
You're confined for three months.
Your Highness.
You faced suspicion
of intimacy with His Majesty.
How can you be so happy now?
You don't understand.
Though we were misunderstood,
I won't have to review memorials
with Jinyun anymore.
Do you think avoiding me
means escaping memorial duty?
Jinyun.
Jinyun, why are you here?
No, you must leave!
We can't be seen together again.
Isn't the Grand Preceptor here?
Take a seat.
Good idea.
This way, we won't be misunderstood.
That is enough.
Your Majesty,
did you come to have me
divine the Empress's safety?
Right.
I read the battle report.
She was ambushed
immediately after setting out.
It's likely an inside job.
I can't stop worrying.
Is she alright?
She's fine.
(Danger)
What's wrong?
How is Xu Yu?
Your Majesty.
Not good.
The divination shows
Her Majesty will face grave peril.
What?
Leading the charge,
storming the battlefield,
and repelling enemies.
Is this useless Xiao Jinyun?
Defeating you at archery last time
could be considered as luck.
But now, he's become so fiercely brave.
Since the Xunfang Pavilion
was destroyed,
your remaining people
have become increasingly useless.
After investigating
Xiao Jinyun for long,
you still can't tell me
why he's become a different man.
Could there truly be
a mystical soul-exchange?
Can someone really change?
What are you implying?
Like Xiao Jinyun and Xu Yu
have their souls swapped?
I don't believe in such heresy.
But there's one thing we must do now.
Time to put the pressure on Dada.
Have them exhaust Xiao Jinyun
in the desert until he dies.
Alright.
(Let's observe Dada's probing results.)
(If Xiao Jinyun survives again,)
(then this astonishing wonder
will be true.)
Yu.
♪Parting clouds
to pluck the waxing moon♪
♪Brewing a pot of bygone years♪
♪Chill flame, window shade,
console my grieving soul♪
♪Drunk through lifetimes
with no dreams returned♪
♪If not for letting go, how could I
bear to shatter this dream♪
♪Returning to drift
through the mortal world♪
♪Like her, like me, like you♪
♪Hairpins carved
with endless sighs and regrets♪
♪Fate laid bare my deepest thoughts♪
♪Like vows, like remorse, like love♪
♪Loving, hurting,
and regretting our late meeting♪
♪Tell me, after all this entanglement,
who regrets it more♪